https://www.alleghenyinstitute.org/privacy-policy/

“Allegheny Institute's research, education and advocacy work to defend taxpayers and businesses against the burdensome taxation, inefficiency and intrusiveness of an ever expanding government.”
Menu  Home
Mission StatementBoard MembersStaff
AccomplishmentsBlogPolicy BriefsReportsMedia
InterviewsEditorialsLRJ: Institute Report
AI Op-EdColin McNickle At LargeContact Us
Support Common Sense Conservative SolutionsTax-deductible donations can be made online or by mailOnline
Click on the linkbelow to donateto the Allegheny Institute
MailAllegheny Institute
305 Mt. Lebanon Blvd.
Suite 208
Pittsburgh, PA 15234
Phone: (412) 440-0079
Email: aipp@alleghenyinstitute.org
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Allegheny Institute for Public Policy collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.alleghenyinstitute.org website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Allegheny Institute for Public Policy.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Allegheny Institute for Public Policy may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
– To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
Allegheny Institute for Public Policy has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: aipp@alleghenyinstitute.org
Sign up to receive our Policy Brief
Email Address:
Enter the letters shown above:*
Sign up to Receive our Blog and Colin McNickle at LargeTax DataAllegheny County Property Taxes
© 2020 | Allegheny Institute. All rights reserved      Disclaimer  |  Privacy Policy  |  Sitemap
Site Development: Hyperdo Media
